I THOUGHT I COULD HANDLE EVERYTHING.
BUT I CAN'T.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
ARE YOU COMING TO SCHOOL?
I THOUGHT I COULD HANDLE EVERYTHING.
BUT I CAN'T.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
TALK REPORTS
IF YOU CAN'T DO IT ALONE,
I'M HERE TO HELP WITH WHATEVER YOU NEED.
I KEEP MISTREATING
PEOPLE WHO SHOW ME AFFECTION.
I FEEL LONELY, AND I'M TO BLAME.
SEMICOLON TATTOO
ANXIETY, DEPRESSION, SUICIDE ATTEMPT
ACCOUNT HOLDER: IVÁN CRUZ CARVALHO
LEAVE THIS GROUP?
LAS ENCINAS SELF-DEFENSE
SARAUL.GOALS HAS HIGHLIGHTED A STORY.
SARA, IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
AREN'T YOU COMING TO THE CLASSES?
I THINK IT'S BEST IF I DON'T…
LAS ENCINAS SELF-DEFENSE
NEW MESSAGE
PEOPLE CARE BECAUSE THEY KNOW THAT,
DEEP DOWN,
YOU HAVE A DAMAGED HEART THAT IS WORTH IT.
FIND IT AND NURTURE IT.
INCOMING CALL: MOM
Subtitle translation by: Toni Navarro